{
    "id": "9e09a170517642c0af02e647acd2d2cc",
    "title": "Primary Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "281b3441eba44af4ab2668f60b29e7b4",
            "title": "Primary Auxiliaries Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She …………………………. returned yet.",
                    "description": "The present perfect is more common with already and yet. Also, use has/have before the past participle form of the verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "isn't",
                        "didn't",
                        "hasn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………………… know what I should do now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "don't",
                        "haven't",
                        "aren't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ……………………………. recognize him.",
                    "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive without to.",
                    "answers": [
                        "aren't",
                        "didn't",
                        "hasn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. you received the invite?",
                    "description": "Use a form of have before the past participle form of the verb. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Have",
                        "Are",
                        "Do"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………….. you see him yesterday?",
                    "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Did",
                        "Had",
                        "Have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where …………………………. she work now?",
                    "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "has",
                        "is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. this your bag?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Is",
                        "Has",
                        "Does"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………………….. not understand the consequences of his action.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "does",
                        "has",
                        "is"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. you call him yesterday?",
                    "description": "Use a form of do before the infinitive. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Had",
                        "Did",
                        "Were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………………… returned the camera he borrowed from me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "didn't",
                        "hasn't",
                        "wasn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What …………………………. you do to provoke him?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "had",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ………………………… you learn about his accident?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "had",
                        "were"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}